gillomdev@gmail.com

GILBERTO LOMELI

1123 Blazewood ST , Riverside, California, United States, 92507 840-228-6860

My primary focus has been on the front-end, where I have cultivated skills in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript over the past four years. Additionally, I have expanded my knowledge by incorporating technologies such as Sass and Bootstrap into my arsenal. My background reflects my passion for learning and my determination to gain experience and knowledge in web and mobile application development.

Professional Experience

Programmer / Web Developer Front-End

June 2023 - April 2024

My stay as a Freelancer lasted 1 year, I was in charge of Managing, Maintaining and Creating software as well as a landing page that could be used to facilitate Internal requirements that included the basic use of languages such as C ++ and Java for a code review as well as the use of others such as JavaScript included with HTML, CSS and Bootstrap to develop more complex activities such as deploying a Static Website that would be used as the main promotional item

Freelancer Front-End October 2022 - April 2023

I worked for a period of 7 months (October 2022 - April 2023), as an independent contractor or known as freelancer for a businessman who was looking to launch a static website regarding his photography work, which consisted of a type of portfolio created with HTML, CSS and JavaScript that showed the quality of his work, additionally as part of the requirements this website was responsive as well as designed under the "Mobile-First" concept so it had great adaptability for any user. Likewise, during this period that my contract lasted, I focused on maintaining the website and incorporating changes desired by the client.

Education

High School Diploma in Software Developer Associate

August 2020 - June 2023 Cetis 100 at Tepic, Nayarit, México

Key Skills

- . Time Managment
- Fast Learner
- Committed and Responsible
- Hungry for Knowledge

Languages

- Spanish
- English
- Russian (Starting to Learn)